<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Mikey O&#39;Brien</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Mikey O&#39;Brien</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 17:29:47 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up PostgreSQL on MacOS</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/setting_up_postgresql_on_macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/setting_up_postgresql_on_macos/</guid>
      <description>For this tutorial we will be using postgres.app from the folks at https://eggerapps.at/ to install and setup a local development server on macOS.
Download and install using the instructions at https://postgresapp.com/
Start postgres from the applications folder Ensure the CLI tools are working by typing,
createdb This should result in the following error if everything was installed correctly,
createdb: database creation failed: ERROR: database &amp;#34;username&amp;#34; already exists To create your development db enter into the console,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving from San Diego to Austin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/moving_from_san_diego_to_austin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/moving_from_san_diego_to_austin/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago an opportunity opened up at work to move to Austin, Texas. I toyed with the idea of making the move but never took it seriously. Next thing you know, the lease on my apartment at the time was about to end and I still had not found a new place to live in San Diego. Queue time to take the decision seriously. Growing up and attending college in San Diego I felt like it would be a good time to experience something new and committed to going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up OpenVPN on GCP</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/setting_up_openvpn_on_gcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/setting_up_openvpn_on_gcp/</guid>
      <description>At work I&#39;ve recently been assigned with analyzing Ransomware samples to improve our detection heuristics. As an extra precaution I&#39;ve set up OpenVPN on a GCP instance to ensure my home IP is not being captured by bad actors.
If you don&#39;t use GCP and would like to use this as a guide for another cloud provider feel free, as the same general steps apply.
Compute Instance Configuration First, create a compute instance from the cloud console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Start</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/a_new_start/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/a_new_start/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been meaning to start a blog for awhile now. In reality, I have a couple times now. Both times life got in the way from fully dedicating the time to write quality posts. Not this time. Seriously. I believe documentating one&#39;s experiences and challenges in life is a rewarding activity (for both parties). I don&#39;t remember how many time&#39;s over the past year and a half of my professional career I&#39;ve looked for the same exact blog to do the same exact thing that I&#39;ve forgotten for the 10th time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a MEVN stack boilerplate</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/creating_a_mevn_stack_boilerplate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/creating_a_mevn_stack_boilerplate/</guid>
      <description>This post will cover the basic steps needed to set up a project using the MEVN stack (mongo, express, vue, and nginx). Prior warning, if you are looking for a tutorial on creating a web application using the MEVN stack you may want to look elsewhere. I&#39;ll only be covering the basic project structure, packages, and tools necessary to get started.
Prerequisites  Basic understanding of javascript Commandline familiarity Familiarity with NPM  To be begin we first need to insure that node is installed on the machine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>